Thank you for your business!
I hope to hear from you again soon.
Sorry to always make you come out this far.
Not at all! I'm more than happy to.
Well then, please excuse me.
Heiwa Dori Shopping Arcade Entrance
Odawara
Kamaboko
Founded Meiji 11
Yama-Jou
Fish
Marufuku
Welcome
to Atami
Heiwa Dori Shopping Arcade
Kinmedai
Tokuzo
We Come to You!
Kinme Cleaning
It's hot.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Oh my.
Have you been waiting long?
I just got here, dear.
I'll open up right away.
May I take your garments first?
Sure, sure.
Welcome.
Welcome!
2x Points Every Tuesday
I'll be with you in a moment.
Kinme-san, it must be so hard
for you working alone.
No, not at all.
I can manage the amount of business I get now.
But when pickups and deliveries
pile up on the weekend, like today,
things can get just a little busy.
Thank you for your patience.
Please allow me to inspect your garments.
Collection Receipt
Location
Name
Date Received
I got that stain about a week ago.
I tried scrubbing, but it wouldn't come out.
So this is a week old?
Can you tell me what caused the stain?
It was a pasta sauce with tomatoes.
Do you think the stain will come out?
You can count on Kinme.
I'll leave you to it, then.
All right!
Kinme Cleaning
Wash It
All Away
Episode 1  You Can Count on Kinme
Orders will be ready
on the 16th
Kinme
Up we go.
Timer
Start
Pause
Welcome!
Okay, let me guess.
Huh?
I'd bet you're in the mood
to eat something sweet!
Oh!
Thank you so much, Yagara-san!
This is just what I needed!
My husband picked them up on a business trip.
I'll make tea, so will you join me?
No, no. I have to head straight back.
Okay, let me grab your garments for you.
Did you ride your bicycle here again?
Hmm? Sure did.
That's really impressive,
considering all the hills.
Thank You for Choosing Us
Kinme Cleaning
Thanks for saying so.
I'm bikin' around Atami and buildin' muscle!
A suit jacket with pants and five dress shirts.
Does that sound right?
Mm-hmm! Thanks.
Oh, right. Listen to what my husband said.
He told me that ever since
we've started coming here,
his suits have gotten
much more comfortable to wear.
Huh? I'm so glad!
I wash all shirts and suits in water here.
Oh? Don't you have to dry clean suits?
Dry cleaning is definitely more common.
This is, well, something of a trade secret...
Oh?
I put each piece in a double mesh laundry bag
and wash them separately in cold water.
Then I hang them to dry overnight.
The next morning,
a very quick spin in the dryer.
As soon as the fabric starts to fluff up,
I give them a very thorough ironing.
Front and back, straightening out
the seams, very, very carefully.
So it should make them very comfortable!
No kidding.
You sure do love doing laundry, don't you?
Yes, I think I do!
It is the one thing I didn't forget, after all.
I'll see you around, Kinme-san!
Thank you very much!
Oh, look at the time.
Closed for the Day
Men's Bath
Women's Bath
Well, hello!
Good evening.
Thanks for your help today.
I was able to remove the stain on your blouse.
You were? That's actually one of my favorites.
Thank you, dear!
Of course!
Be sure to turn off the hot water
Well, I'm off. Have a good night.
Good night.
Just another day's work.
Women's Bath
Good night, ma'am!
Yes, good night! See you soon!
Oh, that's right. It was today.
No wonder there are so many
people out and about.
In that case, maybe I'll do
just a little more work
with this playing in the background.
Wash It All Away
Kinme Cleaning
Gift Shop
Atsuei Dried Fish Store
Oh, it's Kinme-san.
G'morning! You sure are up early.
Do you have the day off?
Ah, no. A little exercise
before opening helps me wake up.
You don't say. So you're all
bright-eyed and bushy-tailed now?
Well, I'm still not much of a morning person.
I never would have guessed.
You always seem to have your act together.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you mean it?
Aww, look at you. There, there.
Well, I should get going. See you later!
Yeah.
Homestyle Inn Ishimochi
I wonder if that's the innkeeper's son.
I think he's supposed to be in high school.
How responsible of him to be helping so early.
Oh! I'd better head back.
Here we go!
Good morning, Poly-chan.
Welcome.
Another busy day.
Let's get to it!
Come on in!
Kinme-san, I've brought
some more things for you today.
Sure! Let me see what we have here.
Oh. Didn't you bring me this one before?
Yes, just once.
I think I remember the fabric.
Orders will be ready
on the 16th
Kinme-san, I'm here to pick up the item I left.
Come on in. May I see your receipt?
Sure.
Is this the right one?
Yes.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Thank you very much!
Hello, this is Kinme Cleaning.
A pickup at 4 PM tomorrow?
Tomorrow
4 PM
Yes, that's fine.
Can I have your address...
Away for a moment.
Be back soon. - Owner
All Pizzas
Welcome.
Come on in!
Aji-san!
I was actually just about to pay you a visit
to bring you this month's rent
and pick up your garments.
Gad, no! I can't have you trying
to spoil me like that.
But it must be difficult for you
to go up and down all these hills.
Same for you, right?
Well, that's true.
Oh, before I forget.
Kinme Wakana
Kinme Cleaning
May Rent
Here's the rent. Thank you very much.
Yup. And thank you too.
Time sure flies, doesn't it?
You've already been here two years.
Yes. Thank you for taking such good care of me.
I ain't done a thing.
Oh, a customer brought me some sweets.
Would you like to stay for tea?
Oh, really? Don't mind if I do.
Great!
It's starting to rain.
The weather was so nice today, too.
Come on in!
Oh... Hello!
Here.
Um, for cleaning?
Um...
Ah, right! Please let me check
your garments, okay?
Would you happen to have a membership card?
One sec.
I've got my mother's.
Kinme Cleaning
We Come to You!
Member: 183
Name: Ishimochi Kashimi
Oh, of course. From Ishimochi-san.
Are you running errands for your mother today?
Yeah, she seems kind of busy.
Huh. You don't say.
Oh. It looks like this has some loose threads.
Would you mind confirming with me?
Yeah.
Uh... what's up?
N-Nothing.
Um, is something wro—
Huh?
Excuse me!
U-Um...
Sandpaper?
Can you tell me how you got this scratch?
Huh? Oh, probably from a concrete wall.
You must have scraped it.
Yeah.
This will only take a minute.
Okay.
Cleaning License Certificate
Registered in Shizuoka Prefecture - Kinme Wakana
It's just a quick fix, but at least
it covered up the scratch a little.
Crazy! But I thought you did laundry!
Well, yes. But this is still
a time-honored cleaning technique.
After buffing the scratch with sandpaper,
I covered it up with
a color-correcting polish. And that's it!
Color-correcting polish...
In addition to clothing,
of course we can clean shoes here,
but we also do cloth and leather bags
as well as various personal items.
I put my heart and soul
into cleaning anything I'm asked to.
Oh! I'm so sorry!
It's just, just... the scratch on your shoe
bothered me so much...
and you didn't even ask me to!
Oh, I've gone and done it again!
Of course, I won't charge you for that,
and if you aren't satisfied,
I'll happily reimburse you for it!
No, it's fine.
Here is your receipt.
I washed it but it still isn't clean!
Well...
that's because of a mismatch
between the kind of stain
and your type of cleaning!
At Kinme Cleaning, we use
washing methods tailored
to the exact type of
cleaning you need.
Thank you very much.
It seems to be raining heavier now.
Um, I'm happy to lend you
this umbrella, if you'd like.
I wouldn't want your shoes getting too wet.
Thank you very much.
I hope to see you again soon.
Um...
Do you think you could clean
my school bag for me sometime?
Sure! You can count on Kinme.
I used to think cleaners
were all basically the same,
We Come to You!
Kinme Cleaning
Contact us anytime
but I think I'm starting to understand
why Mom switched to this place recently.
Kinme's
Quick Memo
Kinme's Quick Memo!
Come on in!
Pleased to meet you. My name is Kinme Wakana.
I'd like to share my day-to-day schedule
with you and show you the layout of the shop!
Kinme-san's Usual Day
(Weekday Example)
My usual day begins with an early-morning jog.
I'm really not a morning person,
Wake Up
Jog
but a jog along the ocean with
all that beautiful scenery wakes me right up.
Shower & Breakfast
When I get back, I start
getting ready for the day's work.
Get Ready to Open
Open Store
Iron clothes left
hanging from
the day before
See customers
(I get many
customers in
the morning,
so things can
get busy)
I usually spend my mornings
ironing and helping customers.
After a lunch break, I see more
customers, treat stains, wash clothes,
Break Time
Grocery
Shopping
I often buy
lunch at the
bread shop
and then dry or hang up the cleaned garments.
Sort collected
garments
Treat stains
and run
several
wash loads
Air dry/hang
washed
garments in
the shade
(from overnight
to 2 days)
Between my other tasks, I also make deliveries.
Other cleaners might do their morning
and afternoon routines the other way around.
When I'm done with work,
I go to the hot spring for a relaxing bath.
See customers
(things get
somewhat
quieter
toward evening)
Make deliveries
between
other tasks
That can become difficult
during the busy season, though.
Close shop
Relax at a
nearby
public bath
or hot spring
Dinner
Balance
the register
And then I go to bed at about 10 PM.
That's how I spend my days.
Sleep
Next, I'll show you the layout of the shop.
When you walk in, my goldfish,
Poly-chan, is right there to greet you!
I keep garments that I'm holding
for customers by the counter.
The ironing board is by the window and
I have a desk for stain removal in the back
by the washer and dryer.
Go even further back
and there's a door to the backyard,
a staircase going up to the second floor,
and even a break room.
So now you know a bit more about my daily
schedule and the layout of Kinme Cleaning.
We at Kinme Cleaning look forward
to continue serving you in the future!
Episode 2 We're Proud of Our Natural Hot Spring
Next time is "We're Proud of
Our Natural Hot Spring."